Finding Aid for James W. Toy Papers 1963-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Spectrum Center 1998-2004
  - Strategic Planning (STP)
    - 2005
      - Team 1, 2 folders (Box 24)
        (teams were responsible for different facets of research)
      - Team 2, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Teams 3 and 4 (Box 24)
      - Team 5 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - 2006 Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Transgender Issues
    - General
      - 1998-1999 (Box 24)
      - 2000 (Box 24)
      - 2001, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - 2002 (Box 25)
    - Bathrooms (Unisex) 2002-2003, blueprints (Box 25)
    - Equality Handbook (Box 25)
    - OSA Working Group 2003 (Box 25)
    - Report to ECAC at Michigan State University 2002 (Box 25)
    - University of Michigan Policies 1993-2004 (Box 25)
- The Peninsula Group (TPG)
  The Peninsula Group (TPG) was formed by a concerned group of LGBT community leaders following the passage of Proposal 2 (Michigan's Constitutional ban on same-sex marriage) in November 2004. It was believed that Michigan needed an LGBT think-tank, using proven strategic planning techniques, so that the collective LGBT community could move forward in a proactive manner to secure equal rights for all. Integral to the strategic planning of the Peninsula Group was a statewide survey in which over 2000 respondents participated. Members of the Peninsula Group informed, facilitated, listened to, made note of, encouraged, and guided, attendees to a consensus. It was agreed that the next step was for several members of the strategic planning team, formally known as the Peninsula Group, to form a Design Team for the proposed Michigan Association of LGBT Organizations.
  - 2005 Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - 2006
    - Correspondence (Box 25)
    - Issue Materials (Box 25)
      (background information on LGBT issues)
    - Presentations (Box 25)
    - Survey Materials (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - 2007
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 26)
    - Hope Fund Grant (Box 26)
    - Presentations
      - Analysis of 44 Leading Michigan LGBT and Ally Organizations (Box 26)
      - Michigan LGBT and Ally Leadership Summit (Box 26)
      - Michigan LGBT Association Design Team Share Out (Box 26)
      - Michigan LGBT Strategy (Box 26)
      - Progress Updates (Box 26)
      - Strategies (Box 26)
      - Surveys (Box 26)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Summit Evaluations (Box 26)
    - Survey Results (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 26)